<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-19T16:24:12.901Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-19T16:24:12.901Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Social Graph Lens Protocol Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51942</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/lens-web3-social-graph-live/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T16:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lens Protocol is a decentralized social graph that allows developers to build web3 social media platforms  on the Polygon network. 
Using Lens, users can mint a profile, follow others, and create and collect posts all on-chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Hash Rates Hit All-Time Highs Despite Bear Market]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51938</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/bitcoin-eth-hashrate-ath/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency miners continue to pump computing power into the Ethereum and Bitcoin networks despite their tokens’ recent price drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June 8 Ropsten Merge Indicates Ethereum’s PoS Transition Is On Track for Q3: Joe Lubin]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51932</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/ethereum-merge-ropsten/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ConsenSys founder Joe Lubin emphasizes Eth2 scalability ahead of the first chain-merge on a public testnet planned for June 8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Has Reduced Commercial Paper Backing USDT by 20% Since April]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51920</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/tether-reduced-commercial-paper-backing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T14:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s largest US dollar stablecoin, Tether (USDT), today announced its first attestation report in six months. The report disclosed that Tether had decreased its commercial paper holdings – short-term commercial debt – by 17% from December 2021 through March 2022, from $24.2B to $20.1B. Tether said it has decreased its commercial paper holdings by …
  Tether Has Reduced Commercial Paper Backing USDT by 20% Since April Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EY And Polygon Unveil ZK and Optimistic Rollup Hybrid]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51909</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/ey-polygon-nightfall-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T10:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accounting firm Ernst & Young and Ethereum scaling company Polygon has launched the mainnet beta of its rollup for businesses, Nightfall. Ernst & Young (EY), one of the ‘Big Four’ financial services behemoths, started work on Nightfall in 2019 to make its customers’ Ethereum transactions private. But the company was so swamped by Ethereum’s high …
  EY And Polygon Unveil ZK and Optimistic Rollup Hybrid Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>