<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-17T08:08:43.538Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-17T08:08:43.538Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Proposes Regulations That Would Recognize Stablecoins As A Form Of Payment]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51725</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/uk-stablecoin-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T02:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Legislation to regulate stablecoins, where used as a means of payment, will be part of the Financial Services and Markets Bill which was announced in the Queen’s Speech,” a spokesman for Her Majesty’s Treasury told The Telegraph.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luna Foundation Guard Spent $3B In Unsuccessful Bid To Defend UST Peg]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51714</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/lfg-3b-bitcoin-fate/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T20:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LFG burned through its Bitcoin reserves in an attempt to shore up UST. Some of its swaps are raising eyebrows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will UST and LUNA Make It Back? Solutions for Terra]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51740</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/will-ust-and-luna-make-it-back-solutions-for-terra/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T07:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Monday, time for a quick take on what’s happened since the apocalyptic events of last week. To recap. UST depegged, Terra’s supposedly blue chip ecosystem death spiraled leading to rampant inflation in the Luna token and catastrophic contagion throughout the entire crypto space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Schmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon Wants to Save Terra by Creating a New Chain With 1B of Tokens for LUNA and UST Holders The proposal also scraps stablecoin design - for now.]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51625</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/do-kwon-terra-revival-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T21:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terra ecosystem’s notorious leader is trying to salvage the resources and talent left behind in the wreckage that is UST’s depegging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Fernau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithmic Stablecoin Landscape Suffers Tremors After Terra Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51614</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/algo-stables-de-peg/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra’s UST collapse has shattered the foundations of the algorithmic stablecoin market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>