<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-24T11:04:41.126Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-24T11:04:41.126Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin and Lockheed Martin To Launch IPFS Into Space]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52147</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/filecoin-ipfs-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T10:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Interplanetary File System (IPFS), a protocol for peer-to-peer file data sharing and storage,  is set to live up to its name through a partnership with Filecoin and U.S. space and weapons company Lockheed Martin.  Filecoin, which relies on IPFS, wants to store an IPFS node on one of Lockheed Martin’s spaceships. When the spaceship …
  Filecoin and Lockheed Martin To Launch IPFS Into Space Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Launches Beta Version of Non-Custodial Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52136</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/gamestop-crypto-wallet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T09:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop, the embattled video game store and meme stock, launched a non-custodial Ethereum browser wallet in beta on Tuesday. Users control their assets and must manage the wallet’s private keys themselves. The wallet is available from the Chrome Web Store for the Chrome and Brave browsers, and an iOS version of the app is “coming …
  GameStop Launches Beta Version of Non-Custodial Crypto Wallet Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Survey Finds 12% of U.S. Adults Held Crypto Last Year]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52124</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/fed-survey-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T09:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly one in eight U.S. adults owned crypto during 2021, according to a survey from the Federal Reserve on May 23. In the central bank’s Economic Well-Being Of U.S. Households in 2021 report, the Fed found that 12% of the 11,000 U.S. adults surveyed held cryptocurrency last year. About 92% of the Americans held crypto …
  Federal Reserve Survey Finds 12% of U.S. Adults Held Crypto Last Year Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest on Terra￼￼]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52120</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/latest-on-terra%ef%bf%bc%ef%bf%bc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GM, Good monday to one and all. Are we in a bear market? Yes, we are and we have been for some time already. The truth is the bottom most likely hasn’t happened yet. I would expect that to be much closer to the previous ATH of 20k. And that will hurt. Details on losses …
  Latest on Terra￼￼ Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Schmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins In Regulators’ Crosshairs After Terra Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52038</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/stablecoin-regulation-roundup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T03:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators around the world are turning their attention to stablecoins after UST's collapse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>