<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-26T15:07:53.814Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-26T15:07:53.814Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave Ends Rewards In Latest Blow To Yield Farmers]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52312</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/aave-ends-rewards/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T10:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave has stopped offering incentives to Ethereum v2 users in its native token, AAVE. At a total value-locked (TVL) of $8.57B, Aave is the third-largest DeFi protocol and the largest decentralized money market.  Aave had incentivized adoption on its v2 deployment since April 2021 by offering AAVE tokens to those that borrowed or supplied crypto. …
  Aave Ends Rewards In Latest Blow To Yield Farmers Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirror Taps Optimism for New Writing NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52303</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/mirror-taps-optimism-for-new-writing-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T09:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 blog platform Mirror now lets writers sell their essays as NFTs. Mirror, a kind of Medium meets Web3, lets bloggers publish essays on the Ethereum blockchain, then vote on the best ones with the platform’s governance token.  Upstart writers could already sell NFTs on the platform and hold crowdsales – they’ve raised $15.36M since …
  Mirror Taps Optimism for New Writing NFTs Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outdated Node Clients Cause Blockchain Reorg on Eth2 Beacon Chain￼]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52290</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/blockchain-reorg-eth2-beacon-chain/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T09:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Eth2 Beacon Chain’s validators fell out of step on May 25 after a client update boosted some clients but caused confusion among validators who hadn’t bothered to upgrade. The incident, called a blockchain reorganization, happens when nodes disagree on the order of the most recent block. Blockchains order blocks – batches of transactions – …
  Outdated Node Clients Cause Blockchain Reorg on Eth2 Beacon Chain￼ Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a16z Raises $4.5 Billion For Its Largest-Ever Crypto Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52271</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/a16z-crypto-fund-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T04:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming, DeFi, zero-knowledge proofs, decentralized social media, self-sovereign identity and layer 1 and 2 infrastructure are among the fund’s areas of focus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WeWork’s Adam Neumann Raises $70M for Crypto Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52255</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/neumann-flowcarbon-70m/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flowcarbon has raised $70M in a token sale led by a16z. It will offer crypto-based carbon credits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>