<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-27T02:54:37.041Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-27T02:54:37.041Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING: Optimism’s $OP Token Could Be Imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52380</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/op-airdrop-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T02:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto users are speculating that Optimism could drop its OP token as early as tomorrow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yyctrader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contrasting The 2022 Market Crash To 2018’s Crypto Winter Crypto winter is a prolonged period characterized by a sustained and general drop in the price of cryptocurrencies which also hinders the enthusiasm for the industry. Is winter coming?]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52364</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/dappradar-winter-is-coming/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T17:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This special report from DappRadar compares the 2018 crypto winter with the current six-month bear trend in an attempt to assess whether a crypto winter is ahead, and what the crypto industry can expect in the upcoming months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DappRadar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PoolTogether Launches NFT Sale to Fund Ongoing Litigation]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52360</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/pooltogether-lawsuit-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T17:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PoolTogether hopes to raise money for ongoing legal expenses through the sale of 'Pooly' NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Fernau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Green Could Air TV Show Without Stolen Ape, Lawyer Says]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52345</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/bored-ape-seth-green-lawyer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T16:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker stole Seth Green’s Bored Ape just weeks before the NFT was set to star in a TV show the Family Guy actor had written about the JPEG. But the show could air even if Green can’t get it back, Jordan Teague, co-founder of web3 law firm The Antifirm, told The Defiant. Green said …
  Seth Green Could Air TV Show Without Stolen Ape, Lawyer Says Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Launches Stablecoin for Mexican Peso]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=52334</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/tether-launches-stablecoin-for-mexican-peso/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T16:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether launched a new stablecoin pegged to the Mexican Peso Thursday, marking the company’s first foray into Latin America while adding to a roster that already includes USD₮, the world’s largest stablecoin by market capitalization.  Dubbed MXN₮, the stablecoin is pegged 1:1 to the Peso, according to Tether, meaning each MXN₮ token is worth one …
  Tether Launches Stablecoin for Mexican Peso Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>