<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-20T15:07:03.499Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-20T15:07:03.499Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism Targets ‘Ethereum Equivalence’ With New L2 Upgrade￼]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51994</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/optimism-upgrade-l2-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum scaling solution Optimism today announced Bedrock, an upgrade that improves speeds and cuts costs for those that trade on the L2. Optimism is a rollup: a Layer 2 scaling solution that batches transactions on another blockchain, then feeds them back to Ethereum as a single transaction. Rollups enjoy the security of Ethereum’s mainnet while …
  Optimism Targets ‘Ethereum Equivalence’ With New L2 Upgrade￼ Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConsenSys Pushes Upgrade for Ethereum Validators Ahead of Q3 Merge]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51984</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/consensys-bonsai-tries/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T10:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ConsenSys, Joe Lubin’s Ethereum software company, has rolled out a new tool it claims will smoothen Ethereum’s transition to Proof of Stake in August, also known as “The Merge.” The tool, “Bonsai Tries State Storage”, came out of early access on May 17. It runs on ConsenSys’s Ethereum client, Hyperledger Besu. State tries are Ethereum …
  ConsenSys Pushes Upgrade for Ethereum Validators Ahead of Q3 Merge Read More »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Haig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Launches US Equities Trading with Stablecoins as a Funding Option]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51966</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/ftx-stocks-stablecoins/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T04:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX now operates the first stock trading platform that allows users to fund their accounts with fiat-backed stablecoins like USDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Social Graph Lens Protocol Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51942</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/lens-web3-social-graph-live/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T16:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lens Protocol is a decentralized social graph that allows developers to build web3 social media platforms  on the Polygon network. 
Using Lens, users can mint a profile, follow others, and create and collect posts all on-chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Hash Rates Hit All-Time Highs Despite Bear Market]]></title>
        <id>https://thedefiant.io/?p=51938</id>
        <link href="https://thedefiant.io/bitcoin-eth-hashrate-ath/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T15:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency miners continue to pump computing power into the Ethereum and Bitcoin networks despite their tokens’ recent price drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandar Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>